&gt;&gt; Good afternoon.
&gt;&gt; 下午好
Welcome to our -- thank you,
欢迎大家  谢谢
thank you.
谢谢
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Good afternoon, and welcome to
大家下午好  欢迎来到
our session on Apple Podcasts.
今天关于 Apple 播客的会议
We are thrilled to be with you
今天我们特别激动能与你们
here today.
聚在一起
I'm James Boggs.
我是 James Boggs
I'm the manager of the Podcasts
我是 Podcasts Business Team
Business Team.
的一位经理
We're going to start with an
首先  我们将会讨论
update on Podcasts worldwide,
播客的一项全球性的更新
and I'll welcome DJ Davis, Lead
然后我会邀请 DJ Davis
Engineering Manager for Podcasts
Podcasts Apple 的首席
Apple.
工程经理
He's going to cover Changes and
来向我们介绍 iOS 11
Enhancements to the App with iOS
为 App 带来的改变及
11.
提升
After that, Garth Jantzen will
之后 Garth Jantzen 将会
give you a brief update on
简单的向我们介绍播客各个方面的
Upgrades and Additions to the
升级及功能的增加
Podcasts Spec. Then, because
我们所介绍的更新将会
you'll be so excited about our
让你们感到十分激动
updates and upgrades, we're
所以我们在最后将会
going to give you some best
为你们提供一些最佳的解决方案
practices and walk you through
并一步一步向你们展示如何
Creating and Launching Your Own
创建自己的
Show.
节目
But first, we want to talk for a
但是首先  我想花点时间谈谈
moment about how we think about
我们对现代播客  包括它的
modern podcasts, long form and
详细模式及音频
audio.
的看法
We get excited about episodic
当我们看到具有娱乐性
content that entertains,
告知性  启发性的单集播客时
informs, and inspires.
我们感到十分兴奋
We get excited in that many of
能使我们的大部分用户感到兴奋的东西
our users have gotten excited
都能使我们
too.
兴奋
In 2016 alone, we served up over
仅仅 2016 年  在 iOS   macOS   Apple tvOS  上
10 billion episode downloads and
我们提供了超过一百亿集
streaming plays across iOS,
的播客下载
macOS and tvOS.
与播放
That's up from 8 billion in 2015
与之前相比  2015 年这一数值是 80 亿
and just under 7 billion in 2014
而在 2014 年  当播客 App
when Podcasts app became
首次在 iOS 8 系统中预装时
preinstalled for the first time
则是不到
on iOS 8.
70 亿
2017 is shaping up to be another
2017 年也即将会随着
banner year as new listeners
新的听众对播客
discover podcasts and the great
及其目录中有趣内容的探索
content inside the catalog.
而成为标志性的一年
We're on track for more than 20
我们预计今年将会有 20% 的
percent growth.
增长
With more than 400,000 podcasts
超过四十万的在线播客
available, our catalog is more
使我们的目录前所未有的
robust than it's ever been.
强大
We have more than a thousand new
我们每周都会收到超过一千份
shows submitted each and every
新的播客
week, so there's always
所以  你们每天都能发现
something new and great to
一些新的  有趣的
discover.
内容
We have more than 14 million
我们的目录中有超过
episodes in the catalog.
一千四百万集播客
That's mostly audio content, but
这些大部分都是音频模式
we have shows and episodes in
同时我们有超过 100 种语言的
more than 100 languages.
节目与单集
Apple Podcast is available in
Apple 播客目前可在 155 个国家访问
155 countries, not only for
这些国家的用户不仅仅可以
distribution of existing shows
获得现在已有的播客节目
but for submission of new shows.
还可以提交新的节目
We're particularly proud to have
能够拥有内容如此多元
such a diverse content catalog,
的目录
and we're also proud to be one
并为全球听众提供一种
of the easiest ways to each a
最简单的获取音频的方式
global audience for audio
我们感到十分
content.
自豪
We want you to join the
我们想要你们也加入进来
incredible collection of media
成为这一由生产高质量播客的
and broadcast organizations
媒体与广播组织所组成的
producing high quality podcasts,
梦幻阵容中的一员
CNN, Disney, Entertainment
这些团体包括 CNN  迪斯尼  娱乐周刊
Weekly, Vanity Fair, Bloomberg,
名利场  彭博
Presa from Spain.
以及西班牙的 Presa
These are just a few of the
这些仅仅是我们全球伙伴的
global lineup.
一部分
We love working with our
同时  我们也很喜欢和全球
partners in public media around
公众媒体伙伴合作
the world as well, whether it's
不管是中央人民广播电台
China National Radio, or CRI,
还是中国国际广播电台
ARD Germany, Radio France, the
德国中央电视台   法国国际广播电台
BBC and, of course, NPR and all
BBC  当然还包括 NPR
the fantastic NPR affiliates
和国内其他优秀的 NPR
here in the US.
下属机构
Our international cohort of
国际化的独立播客网络
independent podcast networks is
正在创造一些
producing some of the most
令人兴奋
exciting content, such as
的内容  比如
scripted comedy from Wondery in
洛杉矶的 Wondery 脚本喜剧
Los Angeles; shows like Reply
布鲁克林 Gimelet
All and Crimetown from Gimlet in
的 Reply All  Crimetown 之类的节目
Brooklyn; comedy and cultural
还有巴黎 Binge Audio 的喜剧与
series from Binge Audio in
文化系列
Paris, and the Great Audiomatic
还有来自印度  孟买总部
programs from their headquarters
the Great Audiomatic
in Mumbai, India.
项目
These, and other Indie
以及许多其他独立制片的
productions, such as Up and
的项目  像来自亚特兰大的 Tenderfoot
Vanished from Tenderfoot in
的 Up and Vanished
Atlanta, have found a home in
都在 Apple 播客中
Apple podcasts.
找到了立足之地
This show, Up and Vanished, is
Up and Vanished 这个节目
an investigative story looking
讲的是一个佐治亚州的选美冠军
at the tragic and mysterious
和一个高中老师
disappearance of a Georgia
充满悲情与神秘色彩的
beauty queen and high school
失踪案件  以及对这一失踪案件所展开的
teacher.
调查
It's an 11-year-old cold case
这个 11 年前的陈年旧案
that has captured an audience
吸引了全球听众的
around the world, and it's
注意
delivered through the dynamic
这个故事由 Payne Lindsey
storytelling of amateur
一个业余的调查员
investigator, Payne Lindsey.
用一种生动的方式进行讲述
On the other end of the Indie
独立制片人的另一方面则是
spectrum is Reid Hoffman and the
Reid Hoffman 及其
founder stories of Masters of
Masters of Scale 的创始故事们
Scale, which are truly epic.
这些故事堪称经典
Hoffman is teaching key business
Hoffman 通过世界上
strategies, skills, and
最优秀的企业家及公司领导者
techniques through the anecdotes
的轶事来教授
of some of the world's best
一些关键的商务
entrepreneurs and business
策略  技能以及技巧
leaders, including Brian Chesky
这些领导人包括 Airbnb的
of Airbnb, and Facebook's Mark
Brian Chesky    Facebook 的
Zuckerberg.
Mark Zuckerberg
The audio production of
Hoffman 搭档的音频
Hoffman's partners, Wait, What?
等等  什么？
is really fun and entertaining.
特别有趣且令人愉快
Also fun and entertaining, Anna
同样有趣的是 Anna
Faris.
Faris 的作品
Her podcast features
她的播客主要是一些
relationship advice from
非专业的好莱坞类的
completely unqualified Hollywood
情感建议
types, and it's seriously funny.
老实说  它们都很好玩
This is an independent
这个节目完全是独立
production, often recorded at
创造的Anna 通常在
her dining room table, and it
她的餐桌旁录制这个节目
features her beloved sidekick
Anna 的小伙伴 Kim 以及他们之间有趣的
Sim and great conversation.
对话是这个节目的特色之一
We recommend you check it out.
你们真的要听听这个节目
So our engineering teams have
我们的工程师团队
done a tremendous amount of work
为了优化播客 App
improving Podcasts app to enable
使之能满足听众对这些
discovery and enjoyment of these
优秀节目的探索和享受
and other great shows.
付出了很多心血
Up next to tell you about
接下来将会由
Podcasts app in iOS 11 is DJ
DJ Davis  我们的工程经理
Davis, our Engineering Manager.
来为我们介绍  iOS 11 上的播客
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, James.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 James
We have some great updates to
iOS 11 系统上的播客 App
Podcasts app in iOS 11, and I'd
有不少重要的更新
love to show them to you now.
我很高兴能向你们展示这些更新
First, you'll notice, we've
首先  你会发现我们对
simplified the app.
这个 App 进行了简化
There are four tabs across the
它的底部现在只有 4 个
bottom.
标签页
We'll take a quick look at each
我们将会逐个介绍它们的
one.
功能
First up, Listen Now.
首先  Listen Now
This is an upgrade to the
这个标签页是之前版本中
unplayed tab from the previous
未播放标签页的
versions of the Podcasts app.
升级
Here, it's easy to resume any
通过这个标签页  你可以随时
episode you've already started
收听你之前未听完的播客
listening to, or you could pick
或者从你已经订阅的播客
the Next episode from any of the
中选取新的
other podcasts that you're
一集
subscribed to.
开始收听
This will be very familiar if
如果你们之前有用过
you used Watch Now in the TV app
TV App 中的现在收看标签页的话
before.
你们对这个功能肯定不会陌生
Next up is Library.
第二个是 Library
This is your personal podcasts
这里相当于你的个人播客库
library, all the podcasts you're
你所订阅
subscribed to, all the episodes
保存的所有播客都能在这里
you've saved.
被找到
You can view downloaded
在这里你也可以看到你下载的
episodes.
播客单集
It's also really easy to get to
通过这个标签页  你能快速找到
your recently added podcasts.
你最近添加的播客
Let's dive into one of those
让我们来看看这个
podcasts.
播客
Here, I can view all the
这里  我可以看到
episodes from the show that I
我想要收听的
need to listen to.
所有博客单集
It's really easy to pick up
你可以通过 Continue Listening
where I left off with Continue
随时从之前离开的
Listening, and from this page, I
位置开始收听
can also view the top episodes
在这个页面  你还可以看到
or scroll down and view all
最流行的播客单集  或者
available episodes.
拉到页面最下方查看所有播客
Here's one of those individual
这个是单集
episodes.
播客
Here, I see the expanded show
这里可以看到节目详情
notes, and I can see exactly how
我可以看到我还有多少
much of this episode I have left
集播客没有
to listen to.
收听
Next up, we have Browse.
接下来就是 Browese 了
This will be very familiar if
如果你们有用过音乐 App
you've used the Music app.
那你们肯定很熟悉这个功能
We'll dive into Featured first.
让我们先来看看 Feature
Each week our editors to scour
每周  我们的编辑都会仔细
all the latest shows and
查阅所有最新的节目与剧集
episodes to bring you the best
以为你们提供最好
of what's new.
最新的播客
We can also look at Top Charts.
我们来看下排行榜
Here, we have all the top
在这里  我们除了可以找到
episodes and shows that are
当前流行的节目
trending right now, and I can
还能浏览热门
also browse featured providers
制作者或者深入
or dive deeper into my favorite
探索“我的最爱”
categories.
目录
And finally, we have Search.
最后就是 Search
Here, you can quickly find any
你可以通过它快速发现
new show or episode in the Apple
Apple 播客目录中最新的
Podcasts catalog or just scope
节目或单集或者仅仅对
that search to your own library.
自己的播客库进行搜索
That's a quick overview of the
以上便是播客在 iOS 11
Podcasts updates in iOS 11.
系统中的更新概述
This is our biggest updates to
这次的更新是自播客首次在
the Podcasts apps since we first
iOS 上发行以来
launched in iOS.
最大规模的更新
We hope you get a chance to
我们衷心希望你们
check it out in the iOS
可以在 iOS developer preveiw
developer preview and give us
中使用一下播客
your feedback.
并为我们提供反馈
Next up, I'd like to bring Garth
接下来  让我们欢迎
Jantzen up to the stage.
Garth Jantzen
He's going to give you an
他将会向你们介绍我们
overview of the updates we're
对 Apple 播客配置的
making to the Apple Podcasts
更新  以确保播客能够
Spec to support some of these
支持 iOS 11 的
great new features in iOS 11.
这些新功能
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks, DJ.
&gt;&gt;  谢谢 DJ
Great to see you all here today.
很高兴今天能见到大家
So, today, we are excited to
今天  我们很兴奋
talk about some updates we're
能和你们讨论我们对
bringing to the Apple Podcasts
Apple 播客 Feed Spec. 所做出的升级
Feed Spec. These updates will
这些升级将会
help podcast creators to take
帮助播客制作者
full advantage of the redesigned
充分利用你们刚刚看到的改版后的 iOS 11
Apple Podcasts app in iOS 11
版的 Apple 播客
that you just saw, while also
同时使
making it easier for listeners
听众能够更方便的
to discover and engage that
发现和关注
content.
这些内容
So, to provide some context, I'd
为了提供一些背景  我将会
like to start with an example of
以你在 iOS 10 的播客
what you might see today in iOS
上订阅新的播客节目时
10 when you subscribe to a new
将会看到的界面
podcast.
为例子
So, when you subscribe to a
当你们订阅新的播客时
podcast, we automatically put
我们会自动将
the latest episode into your
该播客的最新一集放到
unplayed episode list, which is
你的未播放列表中
great for most podcasts.
这种方式适用于大部分播客
But in the case of this example,
但在我们所举的这个例子中
there's a couple of problems.
你会看到这个做法存在一些问题
First, as you can see, this is
首先  你会看到这个播客是
Episode 4 of what looks to be
第二季的
Season 2.
第四集
So, in the case of this podcast,
而这个播客
it's actually intended to start
事实上应该从
from the beginning with Episode
第二季的第一集
1 of Season 2.
开始
Also, it required that the
这种做法还要求
podcast author put both the
播客的作者将第几季和
season number and the episode
第几集放在
number in front of the title,
标题的前面
which isn't the best user
这个用户体验并不
experience.
友好
So, going over to the feed tab
当我在寻找第一  第二
when I look for Episode 1, 2,
和第三集时
and 3, I find that they're in
我发现它们的 feed tab 的顺序
the wrong order, and it's
是错误的这导致
difficult to add those episodes
我很难按正确的
over to my unplayed list so I
顺序将它们
can start from the beginning and
添加到我的
listen through in the correct
未播放
order.
列表中
So, all I can say is that we
那么我认为在这个方面
think we can do better here.
我们还可以做的更好
So, to start, we're happy to
我们很高兴的宣布
announce support for podcast
iOS 11 版将支持季播型
seasons in iOS 11.
播客
So, seasons will allow
季播型允许
podcasters to group together
播客们按照
episodes where it makes sense
播客的内容相关性将
for their podcast content, and
它们分为一季
within a season they'll also be
在每一季里  他们还可以
able to choose the order in
选择这些剧集的
which those episodes are
展示顺序
presented, whether it's newest
可以从最新到最老
to oldest, or oldest to newest.
也可以从最早到最近
And utilizing the other tags
加上我们即将采用的
we're about to talk about that
其他新的标签
we're adding, we'll be able to
我们的季名将会更好  同时标题
present nice season headers and
也能更准确的
concise titles to best present
展示单集的
the content.
内容
New subscribers will also get
当有新的订阅时
full, the full current season
当前季中的所有单集
automatically moved into their
都会自动添加到
Library in a new section called
订阅者播放库中新推出的一个
My Episodes, which is going to
名为我的单集的部分中
be great.
这种方式挺好的
We have a Quick Play action that
我们还有一个快速播放的功能
will allow listeners to start
这个功可让听众快速地从头开始收听
from the beginning, as intended,
播客  或者
or pick up right where they left
从他们上次
off.
离开的地方开始继续收听
So, now, let's look at the Spec
现在让我们来看一下 Spec
and see how all this ties
了解一下这些是如何
together.
联系在一起的
So, first, we have a new tag for
首先  播客将会有一个
a podcast called Podcast type,
新的标签叫作播客类型
and iOS 11, we're starting off
iOS 11 中将会有两种
with two podcast types, episodic
播客类型  Episodic 和
and serial.
Serial
So, first, episodic.
Episodic
This is the default podcast
这是一种默认的播客类型
type, and the one you're used to
也是我们在 Apple 播客中
seeing in Apple Podcasts today.
常见到的类型
This is best for standalone
这种类型适合播放顺序
episodes where listening order
并不是十分重要的
isn't super important.
独立剧集
New subscribers as of today will
现在  订阅者可以收到
receive the latest episode or
最新的单集如果你订阅的是季播型播客
the entire season, starting with
你会收到由最新一集
the latest episode, if you're
开始的一整季
using seasons.
播客
So, serialize, this is new in
Serialize 是 iOS 11 版
iOS 11.
播客的新功能
We're really excited about this.
这个新增的功能让我们感到很兴奋
This is great where episodes are
这一功能适合需要按时间顺序发展
recommended from beginning, from
需要从头到尾去收听
oldest to newest, and it's great
或者叙事性强
for narrative, storytelling-type
的播客
podcasts, where it's important
因为对这些播客
to start from the beginning of a
而言  是否能从一季或者一个节目的
season or show.
开头开始播放是很重要的
New subscribers will receive the
当订阅新的播客时
first episode in their Library,
用户可以在他们的播客库中
or the entire season, starting
找到最新的单集播客
with the latest episode, with
如果用户订阅的是季播型播客
the first episode if they're
那他们就会收到从最新一集开始的
using seasons.
完整一季的播客
So, next is title, which is a
接下来是标题这个新
new tag, and it's intended for
标签这个标签
just the title of the episode.
主要用于标题
We're asking that you leave off
我们希望你们的播客标题中
the podcast title, the episode
不再需要期数
number, season number, and the
季数以及
dates.
日期
We're going to use this
我们将会根据
differently, depending on the
你们播客的类型
context of your podcast type.
对这个功能进行不同的应用
So, in this screen, you can see
你们可以看到
that we're combining it with
我们将这个功能和其他的
some other metadata; in this
元数据组合在一起
case, episode number, to best
比如在这个例子里和
represent an episode from a
期数结合  这对于系列性的播客
serial podcast where episode
来说是很
number is important.
重要的
And then, here, to best
而在这里  标题这个标签
represent an episode from an
可以恰当的展示
episodic podcast, where episode
非系列性的剧集内容
number isn't as important.
因为期数对这种播客并不是很重要
So, next, episode number.
接下来让我们看看期数
So, this is a new tag, and
这个新标签
starting with your first episode
从你播客中的第一集
in your podcast, every episode
开始  每一集播客都应该要有
should have an incremental
一个递增的
number.
数字
If you're using seasons, the
如果你的播客是季播型的
episode number should be
那么你的期数应特定于
specific to that season.
所在的季
Then, we have season number.
接着  季数
Every episode that's associated
所有与特定季相关的单集
with a particular season should
都应该使用同一个
use the same season number.
季数
We'll collect all the episodes
我们会将所有相关的
together and present them as
单集进行整理
seasons to listen to with a nice
以一个有着醒目标题的季的
header.
形式向大家展示
We'll also give precedent to
在你的播客页面
your latest season first on your
我们将会放上你最新一季
podcast page.
的播客
So, using a combination of
通过名称
episode title, episode number,
期数  以及
and season number, we can choose
季数的组合
how to best represent that
我们可以选择如何在 App 里面的不同
content in different parts of
页面用最佳的方式展示播客的内容
the app, as you can see here.
正如你现在所看到的一样
So, next is summary tag.
接下来是总结标签
This is an existing tag, and
这个标签在之前的播客中就已经存在
this is the tag that we're
我们建议你们可以
recommending you use to store a
用这个标签来
descriptive sentence that best
写一句最能代表这一集播客的
represents that episode.
介绍
We'll use this in multiple
这个标签将会在 App 中
places in the app, so we're
多个地方应用所以我们需要你们
asking that you leave out HTML,
不要使用 HTML CDATA
CDATA, rich text formatting.
以及多信息文本格式
In fact, we'll strip that out
我们之所以要去掉这些东西
because that will let us handle
是为了处理截断
the truncation, and it'll let us
并在 App 的不同
handle that description in
部分处理
different parts of the app.
这些描述
So, if you're using a content
如果你现在正在使用的
management system that might
内容管理系统可能会提前
truncate that beforehand, we're
将它截断的话  我们建议
asking that you leave that, that
你们不要管它
you don't do that so that we can
这样我们就可以处理它
handle that and best present it.
使之以最好的方式展示出来
So, content encoded, this is
content encode 这是专门为你
specific for your episode notes,
的剧集内容服务的
and this is where you're going
你可以将你的
to want to put that rich text,
多信息文本
HTML, links.
HTML 以及链接放在这里
We support paragraphs, lists,
这个功能支持段落  表格
bold and italics, and we're
加粗以及斜体
going to use this on the Listen
我们将会将这部分放到
Now view, as well within the
现在收听以及剧集详情
Episode Detail view, so
的界面这样
listeners can easily access any
听众在听你的播客
links and notes while they
的时候  就可以随时随地
listen to your episode.
浏览这些链接以及文本
Another exciting update, we have
另外一个激动人心的更新便是
podcast type.
单集播客
We also have episode type.
也有类型了
So, in iOS 11, we're coming out
在 iOS 11 系统中  我们将会提供
with three episode types, a
三种单集类型
full, trailer and bonus.
完整版  预告版  以及福利版
So, full is the default episode
完整版是默认的单集类型
type, and it represents a
也就是你现在所能看到
standard episode that you'd
的标准
expect today.
单集
Trailer is a great new episode
预告版是一个全新的单集类型
type that can be either a
它既可以是单集播客的预告
podcast level trailer or a
也可以是某季播客的预告
season level trailer, depending
这取决于它的标题中
on if there's a season number
是否有
present.
季数
And this is great for teaser
这种类型适合在你推出
trailers before you've launched
节目之前用来预热
your show, or if you want to
或者在新一季推出前
highlight a trailer for a new
用预告片
season.
来吸引受众注意
Bonus is for an episode that
福利版适用于
contains bonus content, which is
含有福利内容的剧集
great for supplemental content
这一种播客适合
associated with an existing
用于对已经发布的剧集
episode.
进行补充
After-show, or review, we'll tie
同时我们会在 UI 上将
them together in the UI, and
回顾以及主要单集
with the main episode, we'll
放在一起
make it look really great.
使它们看起来很棒
So, we're really excited to see
想到播客们将如何
how podcasters utilize these new
运用这些新的单集
episode types to make their
类型来使他们的内容
content even more engaging.
更加吸引人  我们就感到十分兴奋
So, lastly, I want to call out
最后  我想提提另外
an existing, another existing
一个已经存在的单集
tag on the episode, the GUID.
标签  GUID
So, GUID is a permanent global
GUID 是一个永久的
unique identifier that specifies
全局唯一标识符  用于
that episode amongst your
对你的播客中的
podcast.
剧集进行赋值
We've seen some cases where
有些用户修改了他们
people end up changing their
的 GUID
GUID, perhaps if you change
你可以修改
hosting companies, or your RSS
你的托管公司  或者你的
URL changes, but it's really
RSS URL  但是千万
important that you not change
不要修改单集
the GUID on an episode.
的 GUID
This can result in duplicate
修改 GUID   可能会导致
episodes showing up in your
你的播客订阅者在
subscribers' Libraries, and it
他们的播客库中看到两个重复的剧集
can even hurt your chart
这甚至会影响到你的图表
placement in the catalog.
在目录的布局
So, those are the highlights of
以上这些便是
some of the updates coming to
Apple Podcast Feed Spec 上
the Apple Podcast Feed Spec.
将会有的一些升级
These and all feed specs can be
所有 feed specs 都能在
found online in our Resources
我们的线上的资源与帮助
and Help section, and we're
部分找到
really excited to see how
我们超级期待看到播客制作者
podcast creators will use these
们利用这些
updates to create even more
升级来为用户们提供
content and better engaging
更多更吸引人
content for our listeners.
的内容
So, now that you've heard our
现在你们已经对我们所做的升级
great updates, I'd like to bring
有所了解  那接下来
James back up to talk about how
便有请 James 上台来为
to make the best podcast
我们介绍如何制作
possible.
有史以来最棒的播客
James.
James
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; All right.
&gt;&gt;  好的
Thanks, Garth.
谢谢 Garth
So, now that you've seen all the
你们已经了解了 iOS 11 系统
new features of Podcasts app for
中播客的新功能
iOS 11, and the tags that we're
也了解了我们刚刚宣布
going to use, that we've just
即将上线来支持
announced, to power those new
这些新功能的标签们
features, let's walk through
那么让我们一起来看看
creating and launching your own
如何制作你自己的
show.
节目
Well, first, you need something
首先  你要有
to say.
一个话题
You need an idea at the center
你需要有一个
of your podcast as a concept
可以作为你之后
that will play out over the
每一集  每一季播客
course of your seasons and your
的中心思想的
episodes.
话题
Podcasts are unique in that
播客的独特之处在于
they're not constrained by the
它并不为传统的媒体形式
formats of traditional media,
所束缚  比如
such as talk radio.
电台的访谈节目
This is a place where great
播客让好故事
stories will play out in long
可以以长音频的方式
form in audio.
得到传播
So, our friends, Maria and John,
所以  我们的朋友 Maria 和 John
they needed a great idea for
需要一个好点子
their podcast project.
来开始他们的播客计划
Maria has her Ph.D. in history,
Maria 是历史学博士
and because she's passionate
她对食物的热情
about food, she knows a lot
使她对全球不同烹饪方式
about the history of different
的历史
cuisines around the world.
都了如指掌
And her sidekick, John, loves to
而她的好友 John 则是
eat.
一个妥妥的吃货
So, what kind of a show could be
那么  什么样的节目
a vehicle for their love of
可以表达他们对美食的热爱
cuisine and maybe force them to
甚至激励他们
do some awesome travel?
踏上一段奇幻的旅行呢
The Very Hungry Tourists; Around
饥饿的旅行者  一口一口
the world, one bite at a time.
吃掉世界
They came up with their concept.
这是他们想到的话题
And now that Maria and John have
既然他们已经想好他们节目的主题
a concept for their show, they
现在他们就要
dive into the research and
进入到
planning phase.
调查和计划阶段
What podcasts out there already
现在发布的播客中有多少与
cover their topic?
他们的内容相似
How could their podcast be
怎样才能使他们的播客
different?
与众不同
Where is their potential
他们的潜在听众是哪些
audience, and how would their
他们要如何
themes play out over the course
在单集中
of their episodes?
体现他们的主题
How would they make their show
怎样才能让这个节目
sustainable?
持续发展
Is this a hobby or a business
这个节目仅仅是他们的爱好
project?
还是一个商业项目
Well, sustainability is, of
持续性是决定一个播客
course, a key to success at
是否成功的关键
podcasts, both creatively and
这个持续性指的是创造和经济的双持续
financially, and Maria and John
Maria 和 John
decide that making their
认为  保持他们
production financially
作品在经济上的可持续
sustainable is important.
是十分重要的
So, they looked at the biggest
所以他们对
and best podcasts in the
商务模式中最大及
business models that they used.
最好的播客进行研究
They found that ads and
发现广告以及
sponsorship are by far the most
赞助是目前最为
common model.
常见的经济支持模式
Post-read ads, in particular are
实践中  Post-read 广告
successful and profitable.
是一种成功且合算的模式
The second model, donation.
第二种模式则是捐款
This is the public media style,
这是公众媒体的模式
listener and community supported
由听众以及社团为播客
model, another great option for
提供支持  这也不失是
podcasts.
一种好的方式
Thirdly, they looked at upsell,
还有第三种方式就是提升销售
which is the idea that the
指的是之前听免费播客
podcast audience coming to the
的听众可以
free podcast could be converted
被转化为
to paying audience members
与这个播客相关
through the for sale products
产品的
related to the content of the
销售
podcast.
对象
So, for example, Maria's
举个例子   Maria
ancient, Book of Ancient Roman
在 iBooks 上出售的
Recipes, available on iBooks,
古罗马食谱一书
was a great target destination
便是一个很好的针对
for the people interested in
喜欢他们播客的听众们
their podcast.
的一个销售产品
When it comes to production
当讨论制作策略时
strategy, Maria and John
Maria 和 John 发现
recognized that some of the most
一些当下最流行的播客
popular podcasts in the world
都是用
used world class recording
世界顶级的
studios.
录音工作室
The pristine sound and extensive
这种设备所录制的高纯度原声
post production that results
配合强大的后期
from this kind of facility gives
能够为你提供
you a high quality of audio
高质量的音频
episodes.
单集
It's fantastic.
这多棒呀
And incidentally, I hope you got
顺便提一句
a chance to try our podcast
希望你们能有机会到楼上
studio here at WWDC, above the
我们 WWDC 的播客工作室
main floor.
参观参观  试一试
We've been around this week, and
我们的播客这个星期
it has been a great success.
就已经上架了  还蛮成功的
Maria and John, of course, they
Maria 和 John 需要的
needed something a little less
是比传统录音室
expensive than a traditional
还要便宜一点的
studio.
方式
They wanted something portable
他们想要一些便携  易用的
and easy to use without the need
设备不需要录音工程师
of an audio engineer or a
或者专职
dedicated producer.
制片人的操作
They found that the built-in mic
他们觉得内置麦克风
and the variety of high quality,
还有各种高质量的第三方
third-party microphones made for
iphone 耳机对他们来说
iPhone sound just great.
就足够了
So, our heroes finished the
就这样子  我们的英雄们就
production plan for Season 1 of
完成了第一季饥饿的旅行者
The Very Hungry Tourists.
的计划
Now, it's time to think about
现在  是时候考虑发布的事情了
launch, and their go to market
这时候  他们要考虑
distribution strategy.
市场分销策略了
But first, they've got to
但是在这之前  他们要想想
consider the visual identity and
他们节目的视觉识别
the metadata of their show.
以及元数据
Cover art and metadata is the
封面艺术以及元数据
product packaging of your
是播客的
podcast.
产品包装
So, the importance of these
所以  这两个元素的
pieces is hard to overstate.
重要性也就不言而喻了
Maria and John, their first pass
Maria 和 John 在他们
at cover art design had some
第一次封面艺术设计时
challenges.
遇到了一些挑战
They've chosen to include both
他们选择将他们的
of their personal production
个人制片公司的标志
company logos on top of their
放在他们主题图像
central image.
的上方
And the central thematic image,
而他们的主题图像
while it's thematically relevant
虽然与他们的主题相关
and appropriate, it's complex,
但是太过于复杂
and it makes the overlaid text
这使用户很难理解
hard to read.
繁复的内容
Also, the font size that they've
而且他们选择的字体太小
chosen, especially on the
很难在移动端上阅读
subtitle, is really small and
特别是
hard to read on mobile.
副标题的大小
So, the duo then run through our
他们对我们针对封面艺术
best practices for cover art,
的清单进行了
using our checklist.
研究
They lay out a 3000 by 3000
设计了一个 3000*3000 像素的
pixel JPEG or PNG compressed to
JPEG 或者 PNG 格式封面
be under 1 megabyte in size, so
并将它的大小压缩到小于 1MB
it's nice and lightweight for
以便于下载
download with a clearly readable
同时还有一个清晰的标题
title and one thematic image or
和居中  主题鲜明的图像或
logo central to the design.
logo
This is a design first for
这个设计主要考虑的是
mobile where most of their
移动端因为他们的大部分潜在听众
potential audience is going to
主要是使用
live on iPhone.
iPhone
So, the second pass at their
所以   Maria 和 John
design was much improved.
的第二版封面得到了很大的提升
Maria and John ran through the
Maria 和 John 根据清单的要求
checklist, and this was the
做出了
result.
这个封面
It' looks great on mobile, and
这个封面在手机上看挺不错的
it becomes the basis for the
也成为了他们播客
visual identity of their
的基础视觉
podcast.
识别
So, this runs across social
这个设计简单  合理  可扩展的设计
media, blogs, traditional media,
将会在社会媒体
and other audience-building
博客  传统媒体
destinations for their
以及其他扩展观众
marketing, a single design
群体
that's reasonable and
中
expandable.
出现
Similarly, Maria and John run
Maria 和 John
through our metadata checklist
用同样的方式研究了我们的
where they land on their
元数据的清单  并设计了一个
concise, attractive title with
准确  引人注目的标题和
thorough descriptions, both at
完整的播客及
the podcast level and the
单集
episode level.
描述
They also make good use of our
他们在 feed 和单集标题中充分
newly announced podcast type and
利用了我们新发布的
episode number tags in their
播客类型  期数以及
feed and, of course, thoughtful
季数标签
episode titles, putting the most
他们将每一集
important information about each
最重要的信息放在
individual episode, such as the
标题的最前方  比如
subject matter or the guests
主题
right in the first bit of text
或者
of the title.
特邀嘉宾
And of course, they provide a
他们还为那些
useful link for those super fans
想要了解更多的
that want to go beyond the
超级粉丝提供了
podcast, connect to [inaudible]
连接网络的有用链接
on the greater Web and then have
使他们可以了解到
more.
更多信息
So, distribution; once Maria and
当 Maria 和 John
John have their podcast episodes
录好了他们的博客单集
recorded, they've designed their
设计好了封面  写好了
cover art, the metadata has been
元数据之后
written, they need a hosting
他们就到了发布这一步
partner to distribute their
这时他们需要一个托管合作伙伴
content.
来帮助他们发布他们的内容
Our podcast resources and help
Apple.com 上播客资源
site on Apple.com features a
和帮助站点有
handy list of Apple podcasts
Apple 播客托管合作伙伴
hosting partners.
的通讯录
These organizations are from
这些组织来自世界各地
different regions around the
提供
world, and they offer us
不同的产品服务
different product packages and
他们的特色以及
features and price points.
价格也大不相同
So, Maria and John shop around
Maria 和 John
for the best package for them.
为他们的发布计划
Launch planning.
精心挑选了最佳的套餐
Now, Maria and John can consider
好了  现在 Maria 和 John 可以
their launch and go to market
考虑发布并制定
plans.
营销计划了
They decide to launch with a
他们决定要先发布
trailer as a teaser bit of
一个预告版播客来
content to drive awareness.
预热  并吸引注意
They also look into marketing,
同时  他们在社会媒体营销方面也下了功夫
social media; of course, paid
这当然包括付费和
and organic.
有机搜索
They look at podcast, app, and
他们通过播客  App
search engine ads to drive
搜索引擎广告来吸引额外的注意
additional awareness and, of
和提高
course, appearances.
曝光率
This is the idea that Maria and
通过这个方式   Maria 和 John
John can not only appear on
不仅仅可以出现在其他
other existing and popular
流行播客中
podcasts to make those audiences
让这些可能对
that are maybe thematically
他们节目主题感兴趣的听众
related to their show aware of
意识到他们提供的
their new content offering, but
新的内容
of course taking advantage too
还可以通过
of any traditional media outlets
传统媒体来曝光
where they can make an
并讨论
appearance and talk about their
他们的
new show as well.
节目
Maria and John also make good
我们为播客设计的
use of our marketing tools for
营销工具也为
podcasts, including our Identity
Maria 和 John 提供了很大的帮助
Guide, which will give you best
这些工具包括识别指南
practices for using our Listen
这个工具能让你用我们的
on Apple Podcasts badges for
Listen on Apple 播客标志
print, web, and broadcast
来打印  上传  以及广播你的
appearances.
播客
The Affiliate Program offers a
The Affiliate Program 为人们提供了
unique way for people to link to
一种独特的与播客相关联的方式
their podcasts, and it features
它还有自己专业的
its own resources site.
资源网站
Additionally, Maria and John
除此之外  Maria 和 John
research and implement our
还对 Banner Buiilder 和
linking tools like Banner
和 Widget Builder 之类的连接工具
Builder and Widget Builder.
进行了研究和应用
Our heroes, they're ready to
终于  他们的播客
submit to Apple Podcasts for
已经可以提交到 Apple 播客
review and approval.
审核了
So, Maria logs into Podcasts
Maria 登陆到她的 Podcasts
Connect, pastes the feed URL
Connect  提交他们托管合作伙伴提供的
from their hosting partner, and
feed url
after approval of their podcast,
审核通过之后
Maria and John launch the Very
Maria 和 John 发布了
Hungry Tourists.
饥饿的旅行者这一播客
What was once merely a moment of
曾经这只是个一瞬间的
inspiration is now a written,
想法  如今成为了
produced, and easily available
现成的  便于获取的
podcast.
播客
The work of audience building
现在需要做的就是观众
now begins, and we wish them
推广了  让我们祝
good luck.
Maria 和 John 好运
We certainly will be listening.
毋庸置疑  我们会持续关注
We'll be listening, but how many
持续收听他们的播客
others are listening?
但会有多少人订阅呢
Once Maria and John launch and
一旦 Maria 和 John 发布了他们的
begin marketing their podcast,
播客并开始营销
of course, they want to know how
他们肯定想知道这个
it's doing.
播客表现的怎么样
Their hosting platform offers a
他们的托管平台能够
nice variety of server side
从服务器的角度提供各种
reporting, which is very useful,
有效的报告
but they want to know what's
但他们还想知道
actually happening on Apple
在 Apple 播客这个应用中所真实发生
Podcasts.
的事情
How many people are listening?
有多少人在听这个节目
How much do they listen?
他们听了多少
Where are they listening?
他们来自哪里
So many questions about audience
Maria 和 John 有着这么多关于
and usage, what could we do to
听众和用户习惯的问题  那我们
help Maria and John?
怎样才能帮到他们呢
Well, we're thrilled to announce
接下来  我们将要宣布一个很激动人心的消息
Podcast Analytics, and we want
Podcast Analytics 上线了
to give you a sneak peek today.
今天我们会让大家先睹为快
Yes, all right.
对  是的
Thank you.
谢谢
We're thrilled to be sharing
我们也很高兴能
this with you.
与你们分享
Our new reporting tool for
我们为 Podcast 制作者
podcast providers will allow you
提供的新的报告工具
to see how much of your podcast
这个工具可以让大家看到
episodes are played and when on
你的播客剧集在 Apple 播客
Apple Podcasts, compare the
上的播放量和播放时间对比
performance of your episodes and
某段时间你的剧集和播客的表现
podcasts over time, and see
判断你的单集哪部分
which parts of your episodes are
比较
more interesting than others.
有趣
Are people skipping over your
听众们跳过的是你延伸的
extended music intro, or maybe
音乐介绍  还是你的第二段
your second mid roll?
中间的部分
We're doing this in a way that
在做这些报告的时候
respects user privacy,
我们会关注保护用户隐私
aggregating usage data rather
关注于使用数据而不是
than sharing individual events.
分享个人事件
Analytics are not tied to
这些分析并不与
individual Apple IDs, and users
个人 Apple ID 相绑定
can reset their identifier at
用户可以随时重置
any time.
他们的标识符
We know that you'll have lots of
我们知道你们肯定有很多问题
questions, and we're excited
而我们对 Podcast Anallytics 的
about Podcast Analytics too, but
诞生也同样感到兴奋  但是
we're still in development, so
Podcast Analytics 当前还处于发展阶段
we're going to ask you to, if
所以我们希望  如果可以的话
you can, hold questions until
请你们将这些问题保留到
Podcast Analytics launches later
今年晚些时候的 Podcast Analytics
this year.
发布会
Launching this week, updates to
这周发布的有 Apple Podcasts Sepc
our Apple Podcasts Spec and the
更新  以及帮助你们
documentation to help you
使用这些更新
implement those changes.
的文档
New Podcasts app in iOS 11
同时发布的还有 iOS 11 开发者预览版上
developer preview with improved
得到页面优化的
presentation of podcasts, and
新的播客 App   以及
the infrastructure for Podcast
Podcast Analytics
Analytics.
的基础架构
There's more information on our
如果你想获得更多信息
Session page on
可以访问我们在
developer.apple.com.
developer.apple.com 的相应界面
Thank you very much.
谢谢